{
    "question": "Pengertian dan contoh adverb of frequency",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "adverb yang menggambarkan frekuensi seseorang melakukan suatu pekerjaan, misalnya setiap hari, atau beberapa kali dalam 1 bulan<br>",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "pengertian\u00a0: kata keterangan yang menyatakan seberapa sering suatu kegiatan yang dilakukan.",
            "attachments": [
                "answer-attachments/pengertian-dan-contoh-adverb-of-frequency-256-1.gif"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "ubahlah-menjadi-indirect-speech-1-kiki-said-whats-will-you-962",
            "question": "Ubahlah menjadi indirect speech!    1. Kiki said '' What's will you buy in the mall?''\r\n2. Mrs. Maria said '' Can you speak englsh well?''\r\n3. Yuda said Tika '' Are you from Surabaya?''",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "kalau kalimatnya pertanyaan sebaiknya jangan pakai &#039;said&#039; tapi pakai &#039;asked (verb 2 dari ask)&#039;, jadinya...<br>1. Kiki asked me what would I buy in the mall : menggunakan me karena menceritakan kembali<br>2. Mrs. Maria asked me if I could speak English very well\u00a0: menggunakan me karena menceritakan kembali<br>3. Yuda asked Tika if\u00a0was she from Surabaya\u00a0: menggunakan she karena menceritakan kembali<br><br>semoga membantu :)",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "1. kiki asked me what would i buy in the mall.<br>2. Mrs. Maria asked me can i speak English well<br>3. Yuda asked Tika was she from Surabaya<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "aku-dapt-tugas-dari-guru-binggris-ku-disusruh-membuat-cerita-sp-750",
            "question": "aku dapt tugas dari guru b.inggris ku disusruh membuat cerita \"spoof\" dari pngalaman pribadi, tapi aku bingung gimana crtanya. tlg bantu ya",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "kamu pasti punya kan pengalaman lucu ,,, kamu tulis aja bhs indonesianya nntik saya coba nerjemahin<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buat-kalimat-pujian-responnya-tentang-memuji-keindahan-alam-me-326",
            "question": "buat kalimat pujian + responnya tentang memuji keindahan alam, memuji mother, father, granpa/ma, teacher, brother and sister, friend, best friend pet, your self",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Me : Mom, you are so beautiful in this night.\nMom : really? You never told me before mommy use beauty fash.\nMe : yes mom, you are A princess for daddy tonight, let tell Daddy, if Daddy shock, ask A opinion about you mom.\nMom : Ok , thankyou my sweetheart, i love you.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-soal-soal-persuading-195",
            "question": "Contoh soal soal persuading",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Why don\u2019t you\ntry our special drink bandrek to warm up your body?\n\n\n\n\n<br><span>\nIf I were you, I\nwould \u2026 ?</span>\n<span>\n\u00a0I\u2019m sure you are\non the right track.?</span>\n\n\n<br><span>\n\u00a0<span>I bet you could\ndo it.?</span></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bisa-gak-buatin-pidato-dari-teks-ini-plastic-surgery-is-not-s-r-624",
            "question": "Bisa gak buatin pidato dari teks ini\u00a0    plastic surgery is not s recent phenimenon, but it was appeared since 3000 years ago. in the past, it was for medical purpose but now it is creating beuty and trend to modify some part of body.\r\nmany people nowaday want to be extraordinary such as animal or less human by plastic surgery. they modifying their faces and bodies to make them more animal like. meny so called 'lizard people' have had their tongues split. a woman who changed her face like a cat. other people gone beyond different kinds of tattoos.\r\nthe people who done outcast actually they lack self respect and have adesperate need for attention. they should be treated by psychiatrist, not plastic surgeons. and we should be aware of society that no longer wants to look human",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "hi people, today i will tell you about plastic surgery. plastic surgery appeared 3000 years ago, in the past, it was for medical purpose but now it is only for a change of appearance. many people nowdays want to have a beautiful or handsome face, in other words &#039;being closer to perfections in the matter of appearance&#039;. but some people have some really weird tastes and they tried to be less human-like, by using plastic surgery, they tried to looks like a lizard or cats, and many other animals. the people that took plastic surgery is usually people who is not satisfied with their looks, or their body. they degraded\u00a0the gods creation, and try to be more &#039;perfect&#039;, however they sometime did not look at the risk. you see, if the surgery failed, then can you even imagine what your body or face would look like? and because of that i highly recommend not to take plastic surgery, and appreciate what god has given to us.\u00a0\u00a0<br><br>^aku tambahin beberapa informasi\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "there-care-many-reasons-for-keeping-dogs-as-pete-in-the-city-area-554",
            "question": "There care many reasons for keeping dogs as Pete in the city area, but many peo- ple feel that keeping pet dogs should not be allowed In the city. Dogs are often not taken care properly. They are kept in small backyards and rarely taken for walks. They are left in the yard all day by themselves while the family rune work. Very little attention is given to the dog and it is not a very good life for it. It is no wonder why these dogs bark and disturb the neighbours and become a nuisance to the community.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 On the other hand, not all people treat their dogs this may and why should the peo- ple receive a lot of pleasure and enjoyment from dog's stifle'? Dogs can make a lonely person's life happy or make wonderful play- mate. It can also teach a child responsibility as they not only Potts lay with the dog, but also need to exercise, feed, and care for the dog.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 I feel that we should be allowed to keep dogs in the city, because ills is taken care of properly, dogs can be a great source of pleasure. As a child / used to enjoy playing and taking care of my pet. There is not greater loyalty a nelson can get than from a well-caned dog.\u00a0    1. Some people do not like the presence of pet dogs In their surroundings because ....\u00a0\u00a0 \r\n(A) the dogs are left in the yards\u00a0 \r\n(B) the dogs are often neglected \r\n(C) the dogs often bark and disturb the neighbours \r\n(D) the dogs play with the owner's child \r\n(E) the dogs guard the security of the enyit onrnent\u00a0 \r\n\r\n2. The main idea of the last paragraph is ....\u00a0\u00a0 \r\n(A) pet dogs are loyal animals \r\n(B) pet dogs are more loyal than humans \r\n(C) dogs can be a great source of pleasure \r\n(D) the writer has no objection to keeping dogs In the city \r\n(E) the writer used to play and took care of his pet when he was a child\u00a0 \r\n\r\n3. We can infer from the text that keeping pet dogs in the city will not cause any problem as long ....\u00a0\u00a0 \r\n(A) the dogs are amusing \r\n(B) the neighbours like having pet dogs \r\n(C) the dogs do not balk at the neighbours \r\n(D) the writer has succeeded in persuading the neighbours \r\n(E) its presence does not disturb the neighbourhood",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1.c.the dogs often bark and disturb the neighbours<br>2.c.dogs can be a great source of pleasure<br>3.e.it&#039;s presence does not disturb the neighbourhood<br>ini menurut jawaban saya :)",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-percakapan-expressions-of-surprise-untuk-dua-orang-622",
            "question": "Contoh percakapan \"Expressions of surprise\" Untuk dua orang?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Dina : Hi dani did you know that everyone in this school is talking about you because\u00a0you are the winner of the sains olympiad?<br>Dani : Wow, what a surprise i can&#039;t believe it<br>Dina : Yeah you are the winner good job my friend<br>Dani : Thanks a lot dina<br>Dina : You&#039;re welcome dani",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-soal-expression-of-suggestioun-478",
            "question": "Contoh soal expression of suggestioun? \u00a0",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "woman ; l think the weather is not friendly enough for us to do outdoor activites.<br>mam ; <br>narator ; what will the mam likely reply with?<br>a. enjoy your flight<br>b.let&#039;s go to the beach.<br>c. yes . we&#039;d better cancel our trip<br>d. l don&#039;t think l can attend the meeting<br><br>jawaban c<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "their-motivationimprove-if-they-858",
            "question": "Their motivation...............(improve) if they..........................(kick) a goal during the first half",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "their motivation increases when the kick goal during the first half<br><br>kalau salah gak apa-apa ya<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-describe-dengan-tema-my-beloved-home-523",
            "question": "Tolong describe dengan tema \"my beloved home\"",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "I live in an ordinary house, but I always feel that I belong here for no reason. My house really cozy, it has 4 rooms with AC inside, 1 kitchen, 3 bathrooms, 1 livingrooms, and a green garden in front of it. My mom always take care of this house. I think it&#039;s right that our house is our palace because we can do what we want no matter what. Two years ago, I almost moved to the other house because there was an accident, and sssttt I can&#039;t tell you, because it&#039;s secret. So I think that&#039;s all",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}